{
    "id": "1c0f2ccec7d94580b3028a0bd99b833d",
    "title": "English Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He had a …………….. interest in arts.",
            "description": "Lasting interest means interest that lasts. ",
            "answers": [
                "lasted",
                "lasting",
                "last"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The wagon driver …………………… the horses.",
            "description": "We need a verb here.",
            "answers": [
                "lash",
                "lashed",
                "lashing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He owed his success …………………… to hard work.",
            "description": "Largely is an adverb. We need an adverb to modify the verb owed. ",
            "answers": [
                "large",
                "largely"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He was ………………………… to see his brother again.",
            "description": "Joyful is an adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "joyed",
                "joyful",
                "joy"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He was not ……………………… in the way he handled the interview.",
            "description": "Judicious means sensible.\r\nJudicial refers to an official decision made by a court.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "judicial",
                "judicious",
                "just"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The lawyers awaited the ………………………. decision of the Supreme Court.",
            "description": "Judicial refers to an official decision made by a court.",
            "answers": [
                "judicial",
                "judicious"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The citizens’ lobby was ……………………….. in changing the election laws.",
            "description": "We need an adjective to complete the verb of incomplete predication here.",
            "answers": [
                "influencing",
                "influenced",
                "influential"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "It was an ………………………… article.",
            "description": "We need an adjective here to modify the noun article.",
            "answers": [
                "information",
                "informative",
                "informed"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The student showed ………………………. in solving the difficult math problem.",
            "description": "We need a noun here. Ingenuous and ingenious are adjectives. ",
            "answers": [
                "ingenuity",
                "ingenuous",
                "ingenious"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "No one ………………………. that dilapidated house.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "inhabitant",
                "inhabitate",
                "inhabits"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The large ………………………. made him quite wealthy.",
            "description": "We need a noun here because the adjective large modifies a noun. ",
            "answers": [
                "inherit",
                "inheritance",
                "inherited"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The ………………………. boys jumped into the pond fully clothed.",
            "description": "We need an adjective to modify the noun boys. ",
            "answers": [
                "impulsive",
                "impulsively",
                "impulse"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}